All right, so let's start overwriting the code to the clicking on the family
我们开始重写 Family 类别上的点击代码
category, opens up the family activity.
打开 Family Activity
Now I'm in the main activity here, and we've done something similar for
现在我位于 MainActivity 中并执行了和 Numbers 类别
the numbers category.
相似的操作
So we don't have the write or
我们不需要从头编写 Family 类别的代码
code for the family category from scratch, because we can simply copy and
因为我们可以直接复制粘贴这里的代码
paste the code here and alter it for the family use case.
并修改下代码即可用于 Family 类别
So I'll start by updating the resource ID to point to the right text view, so
我先更新下资源 ID 并指向正确的 TextView
we want it to call family instead.
我们将其称为 family
And once we find the right text for you in this view hierarchy.
在视图层级里找到正确的 TextView 后
I want to store it in a variable called family.
我将其存储在变量 family 中
I can't leave it as numbers because in a single method I can't define a variable
我不能将其保留为 numbers 因为在一个方法中
with the same name twice.
我不能定义具有同一名称的变量两次
We need to pick different names for each variable.
我们需要为每个变量选择不同的名称
So let's go ahead and
我们更新下注释
also update the comments to refer to the family category instead.
指代 family 类别
Next, I need to modify the set on click listener.
接着需要修改 setOnClickListener
So that it refers to the family view.
使其指代的是 family 视图
Now, let's update the intent code.
现在更新下 intent 代码
Here I've created an intent with the current main activity as the context,
这里我创建了一个 intent 并将当前的 MainActivity 当做上下文
and I need to modify this.
我需要修改下这个
So that the family activity is a class that it goes to.
使其指代的类是 FamilyActivity
Then when we start the activity with this line of code.
当我们用这行代码来启动该 Activity 时
We need to make sure that it goes to the family intent.
我们需要确保它转到的是 Family intent
So let's modify it here and here.
所以修改下这里和这里
As well as remember to update the comments.
同时还要更新下评论
Now I'm going to do the same for the colors activity and
现在我对 Colors Activity 和
the phrases activity.
Phrases Activity 执行相同的操作
Now after making those code changes let's test the app on our device.
进行这些代码更改后 我们在设备上测试下该应用
So let's click into all the activities and see that that works.
我们点击下所有的 Activity 看看是否能运行
So first numbers, that's looking good.
首先是 Numbers 看起来没问题
Family members Nice colors.
Family Members 没问题 Colors
And then lastly, phrases, perfect.
最后是 Phrases 没问题
So I did notice that some of the activities still say Miwok at the top
我注意到某些 Activity 仍然在顶部显示 Miwok 字样
instead of the category name.
而不是对应的类别名称
So if you remember in an earlier coding exercise, we actually fix this for
记得在之前的编程练习中 我们实际上
the numbers activity and we did so
为 Numbers Activity 解决了该问题
by modifying its activity tag in the androidmanifest.xml file.
方法是在 AndroidManifest.xml 文件中修改其 Activity 标记
So let's go ahead and do this for all the other activities.
我们为所有其他 Activity 也执行这一操作
So we want the label for the family activity to be the text family and
我们希望 Family Activity 的标签显示文字 Family
we had that stored in the at string resource called category_family.
并将其存储在 @string 资源中 叫做 category_family
So I want to make that modification, and Android manifest, and
所以我在 AndroidManifest 中做出这一修改
I'll repeat the same thing for the other activities.
并对其他 Activity 重复相同的操作流程
Let's go ahead and test it one more time.
再测试一次
Now when we open each category,
现在当我们打开每个类别时
the category name appears at the top of the activity.
在 Activity 的顶部会出现相应的类别名称
Perfect. That brings us to the end of all
太棒了 第一节课的所有编程练习
the coding exercises for lesson one.
到此就结束了
Congratulations.
恭喜大家
[APPLAUSE]
[掌声]